[{"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:05:12", "question": "In which of these directions can most standard elevators travel?", "answers": [{"text": "North by northwest", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Up", "correct": true, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Left", "correct": false, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 1}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:06:15", "question": "Which of these statements appears in the famous \u201cSermon on the Mount\u201d in the Bible?", "answers": [{"text": "My car has a leak", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Knee bo", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "C Answer", "correct": true, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 2}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:06:46", "question": "In what sport would you most likely use the term \u201cbullseye\u201d?", "answers": [{"text": "Golf", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Shuffleboard", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Darts", "correct": true, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 3}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:07:19", "question": "The speed of sound is named for what Austrian physicist?", "answers": [{"text": "Hans Warp", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Klaus Z\u00fcm", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Ernst Mach", "correct": true, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 4}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:07:51", "question": "When used as a slang term for money, how much is a \u201crack\u201d?", "answers": [{"text": "$20", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "$100", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "$1000", "correct": true, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 5}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:08:35", "question": "For what object did \u201cTime\u201d magazine bend the rules for its \u201cPerson of the Year\u201d award?", "answers": [{"text": "Mirror", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Television", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Computer", "correct": true, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 6}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:09:17", "question": "The 2017 fantasy novel \u201cThe Dark Prophecy\u201d is set in the same universe as what other novel?", "answers": [{"text": "The Lightning Thief", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Answer B", "correct": true, "choice": "B"},{"text": "Answer C", "correct": false, "choice": "C"} ], "question_num": 7}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:09:57", "question": "The first moons discovered orbiting a planet other than Earth are known as what?", "answers": [{"text": "Newtonian", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Galilean", "correct": true, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Copernican", "correct": false, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 8}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:10:37", "question": "Which of these words means the opposite of \u201cdeasil\u201d?", "answers": [{"text": "Catty-corner", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Widdershins", "correct": true, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Clockwise", "correct": false, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 9}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:11:29", "question": "Which of these disputed territories is NOT claimed by the nation of Georgia?", "answers": [{"text": "Transnistria", "correct": true, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Abkhazia", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "South Ossetia", "correct": false, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 10}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:12:17", "question": "Which of these Triple Crown-winning horses ran the Kentucky Derby the fastest?", "answers": [{"text": "War Admiral", "correct": false, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "American Pharoah", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Seattle Slew", "correct": true, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 11}, {"timestamp": "2018-05-06 01:13:35", "question": "The lyric \u201cdark side of the moon\u201d is sung in what Pink Floyd song?", "answers": [{"text": "Brain Damage", "correct": true, "choice": "A"}, {"text": "Eclipse", "correct": false, "choice": "B"}, {"text": "Any Colour You Like", "correct": false, "choice": "C"}], "question_num": 12}]